https://www.dartswdf.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.dartswdf.com.
WDF Data Protection Officer Taina Nurmela
You may contact us via WDF Contact Form
Read more about World Darts Federation from Contacts and Federation page
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Contact forms
We use contact forms and we use Google spam detection options. If you prefer not to use that, you may contact us via email available in WDF Directory, in https://www.dartswdf.com/federation/
Website uses also SSL certificates, so you can send contact form via secured connection.
Cookies
WordPress is a free and open-source content management system (CMS)
Session Cookies: These cookies store information about the activities users perform during a single session. They are used to persist data about your activities as you browse through a site but are erased at the end of your session.
If you don’t want i.e. Google Chrome to remember your activity, you can browse the web privately in Incognito mode.
Comments
We do not use comments in our website.
Media
If you provide images to the website, you should avoid provide images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include links and embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We analyse website use and i.e. broken links, so we can get website better. No personal information is collected for that purpose. IP address is anonymised.
Who we share your data with
Website data users are WDF executives for our federation statistics and website development purposes.
How long we retain your data
When we collect data in way we ensure that your identity can be safe, we can keep collected data if we need for our statistics purposes, mainly 1-2 years.
What rights you have over your data
You can always ask about your data and correct if there is error.
Where we send your data
Contact form use be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Our website host is Hosting Ireland. Data Centre facilities located in Ireland. Hosting and storage of your data takes place in BT Citywest Datacentre in Dublin, Ireland. More information of their Privacy Policy https://www.hostingireland.ie/privacy-policy.php
Your contact information
You may contact us via contact form or you may find WDF Executives and Officials contact information from https://www.dartswdf.com/federation/
Additional information
Federation – Legal and Operational Data
As international sports federation we do keep records of our member bodies with their contact information and contact persons. We have annual review for that information. We publish WDF Directory for players to find their own federation. Only Country, Principal Contact name, role and email.
We publish WDF news posts, ranking results and tables in our website.
We also publish WDF List of Disciplined Players and Officials based on rules https://www.dartswdf.com/rules/
How we protect your data
We keep our website updated and we use secure connections (https). We keep our Executives and officials informed and we continuously study them about privacy and how to safely use information systems.
What data breach procedures we have in place
We have internal instructions for potential data breach.
What third parties we receive data from
From our member bodies, tournament organisers, other parties from World of Darts and International Sport and related to Anti-Doping our WDF Anti-Doping Officers process data in The Anti-Doping Administration & Management System (ADAMS) with WADA and CCES
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Nothing in our website or in other processing.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
No known requirements.
We respect your privacy and follow EU Regulation (EU) 2016/679 General Data Protection Regulation, FULL TEXT
CHAPTER II
Principles
Article 5
Principles relating to processing of personal data
1. Personal data shall be:
(a) processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner in relation to the data subject (‘lawfulness, fairness and transparency’);
(b) collected for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes and not further processed in a manner that is incompatible with those purposes; further processing for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes shall, in accordance with Article 89(1), not be considered to be incompatible with the initial purposes (‘purpose limitation’);
(c) adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in relation to the purposes for which they are processed (‘data minimisation’);
(d) accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date; every reasonable step must be taken to ensure that personal data that are inaccurate, having regard to the purposes for which they are processed, are erased or rectified without delay (‘accuracy’);
(e) kept in a form which permits identification of data subjects for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are processed; personal data may be stored for longer periods insofar as the personal data will be processed solely for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes in accordance with Article 89(1) subject to implementation of the appropriate technical and organisational measures required by this Regulation in order to safeguard the rights and freedoms of the data subject (‘storage limitation’);
(f) processed in a manner that ensures appropriate security of the personal data, including protection against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage, using appropriate technical or organisational measures (‘integrity and confidentiality’).
BULL’S DARTS – STORE
WDF Info 10/12 WDF Calendar – Updated 10/12
WDF Tables – updated 15/11
Annual rolling table updates – removed old points 2019
Search
Search for:
Search
Follow Us
Officials Login Login to Officials Area
Anti-Doping reminder – Are you taking medication? If you are this message may apply to you.
CLICK THIS AND READ!
Privacy Policy WDF Privacy Policy information available here
Categories
News (3)
WDF Cups (61)
WDF Federation News (68)
WDF Member & Partner News (62)
WDF Ranking & Tournaments (848)
Archives Archives
Select Month
December 2020  (2)
November 2020  (5)
October 2020  (5)
September 2020  (1)
August 2020  (1)
July 2020  (1)
May 2020  (1)
April 2020  (2)
March 2020  (10)
February 2020  (13)
January 2020  (8)
December 2019  (6)
November 2019  (22)
October 2019  (11)
September 2019  (13)
August 2019  (8)
July 2019  (4)
June 2019  (6)
May 2019  (13)
April 2019  (11)
March 2019  (12)
February 2019  (6)
January 2019  (11)
December 2018  (6)
November 2018  (13)
October 2018  (11)
September 2018  (9)
August 2018  (7)
July 2018  (6)
June 2018  (10)
May 2018  (15)
April 2018  (13)
March 2018  (10)
February 2018  (14)
January 2018  (10)
December 2017  (7)
November 2017  (6)
October 2017  (12)
September 2017  (12)
August 2017  (11)
July 2017  (5)
June 2017  (8)
May 2017  (16)
April 2017  (16)
March 2017  (7)
February 2017  (6)
January 2017  (8)
December 2016  (7)
November 2016  (13)
October 2016  (12)
September 2016  (6)
August 2016  (13)
July 2016  (6)
June 2016  (8)
May 2016  (11)
April 2016  (17)
March 2016  (10)
February 2016  (5)
January 2016  (10)
December 2015  (6)
November 2015  (10)
October 2015  (11)
September 2015  (2)
August 2015  (10)
July 2015  (6)
June 2015  (6)
May 2015  (14)
April 2015  (7)
March 2015  (9)
February 2015  (2)
January 2015  (8)
December 2014  (3)
November 2014  (8)
October 2014  (11)
September 2014  (6)
August 2014  (4)
July 2014  (5)
June 2014  (8)
May 2014  (12)
April 2014  (8)
March 2014  (9)
February 2014  (3)
January 2014  (5)
December 2013  (3)
November 2013  (15)
October 2013  (10)
September 2013  (12)
August 2013  (6)
July 2013  (6)
June 2013  (10)
May 2013  (11)
April 2013  (7)
March 2013  (9)
February 2013  (9)
January 2013  (6)
December 2012  (8)
November 2012  (13)
October 2012  (11)
September 2012  (11)
August 2012  (7)
July 2012  (5)
June 2012  (7)
May 2012  (10)
April 2012  (6)
March 2012  (8)
February 2012  (7)
January 2012  (6)
December 2011  (6)
November 2011  (11)
October 2011  (13)
September 2011  (22)
August 2011  (9)
July 2011  (6)
June 2011  (7)
May 2011  (7)
April 2011  (4)
March 2011  (8)
February 2011  (7)
January 2011  (5)
December 2010  (5)
November 2010  (8)
October 2010  (9)
